Bryant Brock

Full-stack software engineer; experienced developing applications and having to gather/organize data from the database, exposing it as a REST API, fetching it from the client (React), and then displaying it. Married, living in Moscow ID.

1377 N Mountain View Rd Moscow, ID 83843

(770) 820-8961

bryantleebrock@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Emsi Burning Glass, Moscow ID — Software Engineer I

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

Programmed new and existing features of Analyst, including a new release SmartReq. Developed the PHP-based api, server-side rendering, and data fetching from the many different emsi APIs (e.g Job Postings Analytics API, Profiles API, and Core LMI API).

ConsignCloud, Moscow ID — Software Engineer & Customer Service Rep

SEPT 2019 - PRESENT

After serving as a Software Engineer and customer support rep for over a year and a half, I moved to a contracting role purely as a Software Engineer. Worked with Senior Software Engineer Jonathan Staab, and programmed a number of features for the software, working both in the large scale Python Werkzeug API and the React/Redux front-end.

Chick-Fil-A, Daphne AL — Team Member

OCT 2015 - AUG 2017

Dealt with every aspect of the business: drive-thru, font-of-house, and even worked as line cook in the back during my time there. I love Chickfila.

EDUCATION

New Saint Andrews College, Moscow ID — B.A.

AUG 2017 - MAY 2021

Mises University, Auburn AL — Certificate

JUL 2020

A week intensive course that counted towards my NSA degree. Dove deep into Austrian economics with lectures, discussions, and even exams.

PROJECTS

${\bf Life\ Beyond\ College\ @\ NSA-Board\ Member}$

Organized speakers for our workshops, worked with other board members to create opportunities for students to think about their future vocation.

TOP SKILLS

Fluent in Python, Javascript, Git, and Bash

Experienced using React, MySql, PostgreSQL, Django, Werkzeug, Flask, Node, Prisma

Experienced with PaaS (AWS and Google Cloud Platform)

Decisive and practical

Effective communicator

Getting to the heart of a problem

Working with a team

Media

Github

https://github.com/bryantbrock

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryantleebrock/

Facebook

https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100009446198128

References

Available on request.